http://australianwomenonline.com/privacy-policy/

Discount Holidays
You are here: Home / Privacy PolicyShare this:TweetEmailMoreShare on TumblrPrintWhatsAppWho we are
Our website address is: http://australianwomenonline.com.
What personal data we collect and why we collect it
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymised string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.
Media
If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.
Contact forms
Cookies
If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.
If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.
When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.
If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.
Analytics
We use Google Analytics to track visitors to our website. Google Analytics mainly uses first-party cookies to report on visitor interactions on this website. Users may disable cookies or delete any individual cookie. Learn how Google uses cookies at https://policies.google.com/technologies/cookies
Google Analytics also supports an optional browser add-on that – once installed and enabled – disables measurement by Google Analytics for any site a user visits. Note that this add-on only disables Google Analytics measurement.
Our website uses Google Analytics with the Google Advertising product, AdWords, and therefore, additional advertising identifiers may be collected. Visitors to this website can opt-out of this feature and manage their settings for this cookie using the Google Ads Settings.
Google Analytics also collects Internet Protocol (IP) addresses to provide and protect the security of the service, and to give website owners a sense of which country, state, or city in the world their users come from (also known as “IP geolocation”). Google Analytics provides a method to mask IPs that are collected but note that website owners have access to their users’ IP addresses even if the website owners do not use Google Analytics.
For more information read the Google Privacy Policy https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en
Who we share your data with
Our website does not share the data you provide in the comments section of this website (name, email address etc.) with any third-party.
How long we retain your data
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.
For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can request to see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.
What rights you have over your data
If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where we send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Our contact information
Additional information
This website uses cookies including third party cookies for advertising purposes. By using this website you consent to the use of these cookies on advertising banners and text links.
How we protect your data
To protect your data, for the time being we no longer offer visitors to this website the option of submitting a comment on our web pages. However, you can submit a comment on a social media accounts: Twitter; Facebook; Linkedin; Pinterest; and Google+
Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
As you may be aware there is new data and privacy legislation coming into effect in Europe on 25th May 2018: GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation). While this legislation has been set in Europe, there are still potential ramifications for Australian websites that receive traffic from Europe and for this reason, we updated our privacy policy on 19th May 2018.
More information on GDPR can be found at http://www.privacy-regulation.eu/en/
What would I be entitled to as a single mother in Australia?
Tips for working women on how to find a reliable plumber in Melbourne
Popular Content
Sexy and Stylish Short Hairstyles for Women Over 60
Moore Weekly Stars
What would I be entitled to as a single mother in Australia?
Get the Hamptons Look for Your Home on a Budget
Aussie Mums open male escort agency catering exclusively to women
Advertise with Australian Women Online
Why Your Workouts Have Become Boring
Jamie Oliver Christmas Recipes using Aussie meat and produce
The 10 Best Side Dishes For Ribs
Spice Up Your Beauty Regime With These Four Apps
Send to Email Address
